PARITA DEY

Android Developer

Address: 11/B, Biswanath Motilal Lane, Bowbazar, Kolkata-700012,

Date of Birth: 1995-07-16

E-mail: paritasampa95@gmail.com

Phone: 8017814108

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/parita-dey-10a0a1115/

Computer Engineer with 2 years of experience in Android Application Development. An autonomous worker committed to enhance working capacity, professional skills, business efficiencies, self-growth to serve and meet company's goals and objectives with sheer determination, commitment and zest.

EXPERIENCE:

PROGRAMMER-IT- DEPARTMENT OF ARCHITECTURE AND PLANNING, IIT KHARAGPUR 2019-06 – Present.

Description: Working as a Programmer-IT (Android Developer) under research project 'Developing Appropriate Software and Hardware for Fully Automated Self Service Bicycle Share System: Pilot Study in IIT Campus (AHB)': sponsored by Ministry of Housing and Urban Affairs (Urban Transport-IV, Desk) Gov.t of India.

JUNIOR PROGRAMMER – DEPARTMENT OF ARCHITECTURE AND PLANNING, IIT KHARAGPUR 2018-06 TO 2019-05

Worked as a Junior Programmer under research project 'Service Level Optimization Between Public Bus and Para-transit Services Along a Transport Corridor (PAT)';-sponsored by Ministry of Urban Development (Urban Transport-IV, Desk) Gov.t of India.

Working as an Android Developer to develop android application for Bicycle Sharing System (PBS)

Link: https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/home/education/news/public-bicycle-sharingsystemdevised-by-researchers-at-iit-kharagpur/articleshow/68664598.cms

SAANCH SOFTWARE SOLUTION PVT LTD (2018-03 - 2018-05)

Description: Internship in android application development.

TWISPRO TECHNOLOGY PVT LTD (2016-01 - 2017-01)

	Description:	Worked	as an	intern	to	develop	android	app	lication.
--	--------------	--------	-------	--------	----	---------	---------	-----	-----------

Project ID: TTPL/DEV/JSV/APPS/ANDROID/143

EDUCATION:

1. BRAINWARE GROUP OF INSTITUTION-SDET, Kolkata, WEST BENGAL (2014-08 - 2018-05)

Computer Science Engineering, DGPA: 8.48

2. ST. JOHNS DIOCESAN GIRLS' HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL, WEST BENGAL (2012 – 2014)

Secondary education in Science, Percentage: 67%

3. HOLY CHILD GIRLS' HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL, WEST BENGAL (2002 – 2012)

Primary Education, Percentage: 78.57

SKILLS:

Android SDK

Git

Firebase

UX

Android Application

Material Design

SQLite

Java Programming Language

C programming Language

php

python